Finding Aid for the Kenneth Rexroth Papers LSC.0175
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 4: Manuscripts by others, 1936-1975; 18.5 boxes (9.25 linear ft.).
  - Subseries 4A: A-Z,., 1936-1975; 17.5 boxes.
    - Squire, James., no date.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 2)
      "Voiceless Trees"; "Waiting on you"
    - Starmer, Glenn., 1966 May 27.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Stephan, Ruth., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 4)
      "The Grievous Sin"
    - Stevenson, Lina., 1962 January 23.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 5)
      Essay for art history class
    - Storm, Hans Otto., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 6)
      "Third Street"
    - Swift, Basil., 1950.; 3 items. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Szerlip, Barbara., no date.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 8)
      Poems and translations; collage
    - Talbot, J. Rand., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 9)
      "Mrs. Mary Johnson" (novel excerpt); "The Possibilities of an Intelligent Regionalism in California"
    - Thompson, Lloyd S., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 10)
      Two Fragments from a "Tune River Anthology"
    - Thornton, Larry., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Tinker, Carol., no date.; 4 items. (Box 92, Folder 12)
      Assorted poems. Includes work by Michael Corr and William Puette
    - Tomlinson, Kerry., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 13)
      Untitled poem with letter on reverse
    - Torregian, Sotere., 1968-70.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 14)
      Poems; "Song for Woman" and letter
    - Truck, Fred., 1973 May 12.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Tucker, Janice., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Turner, John., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 17)
      "Circus for Pia"
    - Umeno, Koichi., no date.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 18)
      "Some A Rose!"
    - Unidentified manuscripts., ca. 1950-1970. (Box 94)
      Six folders of unidentified manuscripts, consisting largely of poetry.
    - Valera, J. Eduardo Pérez., ca. 1970.; 1 item. (Box 92, Folder 19)
      "Towards a Transcultural Philosophy"
    - Van Ghent, Dorothy., 1936.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 20)
      Untitled MS of critical work on Rexroth, Laura Riding, and Gertrude Stein; poems.
    - Verden, Paul., 1962 June 18.; 2 items. (Box 92, Folder 21)
      "The Partridge Dance"; letter
    - Viglini, Janelle., no date.; 6 items. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Vogel, Sheldon., 1973 November.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 2)
      Poems with handwritten note on accompanying envelope
    - Walton, Dennis., no date.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Ward, Douglas., no date.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 4)
      "The Johns' Saga"
    - Waterman, Priscillia., 1961.; 3 items. (Box 93, Folder 5)
      Assorted poetry; letter
    - Weir, J.M., 1958 January.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 6)
      Untitled poem, letter
    - Weisberg, Arthur., no date.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 7)
      "Wanderings on a War Motif no. 1"
    - Wesolowski, Jim., no date.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Westerman, Georg., no date.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 9)
      Selected poems entitled "Of Futures Past"; cover letter by Charles Whitt
    - Whalen, Philip., 1955 May.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Williams, John., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 11)
      Lengthy manuscript of poems; cover letter
    - Williams, Reece., 1960 April 27.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 12)
      Poems, letter from John [last name illegible] to Rexroth introducing poems
    - Williamson, Ione., no date.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Wilson, John., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 14)
      "Portrait of a Woman by the River"; letter
    - Wittler, Janet., 1974.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 15)
      Poems; paperwork related to Wittler's application to study with Rexroth through the International Community College
    - Woodcock, George., no date.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 16)
      "Currency Reform and American Agrarian Populism"
    - Zachariou, Peter., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 17)
      "Holy Water"; letter
    - Zackheim, Bernard Baruch., 1973.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 18)
      "Persecution"
    - Zorn, Ronald., 1960 April 26.; 2 items. (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Zukofsky, Celia T., no date.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 20)
      Assorted poems and a music score
    - Zukofsky, Louis., 1931.; 1 item. (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 4B: Lonergan Conference papers,., 1970; 1 box.
    Copies of essays submitted by various authors for the First International Lonergan Conference. Rexroth served on the conference committee.
    - First International Lonergan Conference papers (folder 1 of 7)., 1970.; 10 items. (Box 110, Folder 19)
      Letter to Kenneth Rexroth; assorted essays
    - First International Lonergan Conference papers (folders 2-6 of 7)., 1970.; 37 items. (Box 111, Folder 1-5)
    - First International Lonergan Conference papers (folder 7 of 7)., 1970.; 4 items. (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Series 5: Miscellaneous, 1925-1974; 15.5 boxes (7.75 linear ft.).
  A. Artwork, 1941-1969 (1 folder).
  B. Audio recordings, 1952-1966 (6 boxes).
  C. Finances and calendars, 1947-1970 (5 boxes).
  D. Kenneth Rexroth Books, 1940-1957 (1 box).
  E. Photographs, 1925-1958 (1 folder).
  F. Travel, 1948-1974 (3.5 boxes).
  - Subseries 5A: Artwork,., 1941-1969; 1 folder.
    Original sketches and artwork. See box 159 for an original pastel by Kenneth Rexroth (gift of Joseph Handler).
    - Artwork., 1941-1969.; 16 items. (Box 95, Folder 1)
      Includes original watercolors, drawings, and caricatures of Rexroth and other subjects. Artists include Barney Howell and Manuel Caipo. See box 159 for an oversize caricature of Rexroth as a Communist, and an original pastel by Rexroth of a fish in a waterfall.
  - Subseries 5B: Audio recordings,., 1952-1966; 6 boxes.
    Tape reels and recordings primarily consisting of lectures, poetry readings, programs, and seminars by Rexroth and others. Preservation reformatting was recommended during the 2005 reprocessing; materials are restricted until further notice. Please inquire in advance for availability.
    - Autobiography I--Unlabeled parts., ca. 1960.; 2 items. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Autobiography I--Parts 4-7., ca. 1960.; 4 items. (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Autobiography I--Parts 8-11., ca. 1960.; 4 items. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Autobiography II--Unlabeled parts., 1959 June.; 2 items. (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Autobiography II--Parts 1, 3., 1959 May.; 2 items. (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Autobiography II--Parts 4, 8., 1959 June.; 2 items. (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Autobiography II--Parts 9-10., 1959.; 2 items. (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, Lee and John Beall., no date.; 2 items. (Box 96, Folder 4)
      Readings.
    - Holiday in Oregon., no date.; 1 item. (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Record.
    - Howard University pilot., no date.; 2 items. (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Jazz Poetry--Miscellaneous., 1957.; 2 items. (Box 96, Folder 7)
      Includes rehearsal for a festival and recording by Lionel Haupton.
    - Jazz Poetry--Rexroth and the Dick Mills Quintet., 1958.; 3 items. (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Jazz Poetry--Rexroth and Dylan Thomas., no date.; 2 items. (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Jazz poetry--Rexroth and Ferlinghetti at the Cellar., ca. 1957-1958.; 6 items. (Box 97, Folder 3-5)
    - Levertov, Denise and Anne Luckhart., 1953, 1966.; 2 items. (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - MacDiarmid, Hugh--A Drunk Man Looks at the Thistle., no date.; 3 items. (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Rexroth--"Books" program., 1952 May, 1955.; 4 items. (Box 98, Folder 3)
      Includes readings by Don Gordon, Naomi Replansky, and Thomas McGrath.
    - Rexroth--"Delay and commercialization of the image of revolt" (lecture)., 1960 May.; 1 item. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Rexroth--"Ice Shall Cover Nineveh"., no date.; 2 items. (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Rexroth--"Men Against the State"., no date.; 2 items. (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Rexroth--Miscellaneous poetry., 1952.; 4 items. (Box 99, Folder 2)
      Includes recordings of Original Narratives of Early American History, and a reading at Reed College.
    - Rexroth--"An outsider looks at the awakening in the church" (lecture)., 1963 October 16.; 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Rexroth--"Penguins and Ilian"., 1952 June 12.; 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Rexroth--Reviews., ca. 1952.; 2 items. (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Rexroth seminar--1st-4th sessions., no date.; 4 items. (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Rexroth seminar--5th-8th sessions., no date.; 4 items. (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Rexroth seminar--9th session., no date.; 1 item. (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Savage, Derek., 1959.; 2 items. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - University of Chicago Poets Round Table and unidentified recordings., ca. 1955.; 4 items. (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 5C: Finances and calendars,., 1947-1970; 5 boxes.
    Personal calendars and records of Rexroth family finances, including income tax forms and receipts for expenses. Arranged chronologically.
    - Addresses., no date.; ca. 100 items. (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Bank of America., 1947-1959.; ca. 100 items. (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
    - Calendars., 1962-1968.; 8 items. (Box 101, Folder 4-5)
    - Calendars., 1971, 1973.; 3 items. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Insurance--Automobile., 1966-1969.; ca. 30 items. (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Insurance--Home., 1960-1966.; ca. 30 items. (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Taxes., 1960.; ca. 20 items. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Taxes., 1961.; ca. 20 items. (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Taxes., 1962.; ca. 25 items. (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Taxes., 1963.; ca. 20 items. (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Taxes., 1964.; ca. 25 items. (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Expenses., 1964.; ca. 25 items. (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Taxes., 1965.; ca. 30 items. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Expenses., 1965.; ca. 100 items. (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Taxes., 1966.; ca. 30 items. (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Expenses., 1966.; ca. 100 items. (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Income., 1966.; ca. 75 items. (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Taxes., 1967.; ca. 30 items. (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Expenses., 1967.; ca. 75 items. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Income., 1967.; ca. 100 items. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Taxes., 1968.; ca. 25 items. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Expenses., 1968.; ca. 75 items. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Royalty income., 1968.; ca. 75 items. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Merrill Lynch., 1968-1969.; ca. 30 items. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Taxes., 1969.; ca. 50 items. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Expenses., 1969.; ca. 100 items. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Taxes., 1970.; ca. 20 items. (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Expenses., 1970.; ca. 100 items. (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Home improvements., 1970.; ca. 20 items. (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Income., 1970.; ca. 100 items. (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 5D: Kenneth Rexroth Books,., 1940-1957; 1 box.
    Bills, correspondence and invoices from Kenneth Rexroth's San Francisco book shop, removed from a binder labeled "Kenneth Rexroth Books." Additional correspondence with publishers may be found in Series 1.
    - Personal effects and bills., 1953-1957.; ca. 100 items. (Box 106, Folder 1-2)
    - A. Zwemmer Ltd., 1950 March 2.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 3)
      Invoice
    - Alfred Wilson Antiquarian Books, Ltd., 1948-1950.; 9 items. (Box 106, Folder 4)
      Check, invoices and letter
    - American Printer., 1948 December.; 2 items. (Box 106, Folder 5)
      Correspondence to Monse Chicago, INC. regarding Fred Goudy's Trajan Title type face
    - Aragat Booksellers., 1948-1949.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 6)
      Invoices and checks
    - Argus Books, Inc., 1948 December 13.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 7)
      Letter
    - Arthur Probsthain., 1948-1950.; 10 items. (Box 106, Folder 8)
      Checks, invoices and letters
    - Atlantis Bookshop., 1948 June-August.; 10 items. (Box 106, Folder 9)
      Correspondence and invoices
    - Barnes and Noble., 1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 10)
      Invoices
    - Beauchamp Bookshop Ltd., 1948-1950.; 6 items. (Box 106, Folder 11)
      Invoices and book lists
    - Bernard Quaritch Ltd., 1948-1950.; 11 items. (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - B.H. Blackwell, Ltd., 1950 May.; 4 items. (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Book Shop (The)., 1949 May 16.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 14)
      Invoice from Donald T. Evans
    - Books INC., 1948.; 5 items. (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Books 'N Things., 1948-1949.; 4 items. (Box 106, Folder 16)
      Invoices and a check
    - Briguglio Book Service., no date.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 17)
      Book lists
    - British Museum., 1948 June 29.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 18)
      Letter from Kenneth Rexroth
    - Dawson's Book Shop., 1948 May 26.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - E. Joseph., 1949 may 12.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Editions Poetry London Ltd., 1948-1948.; 15 items. (Box 106, Folder 21)
      Check, invoices, and letter
    - Faber & Faber Ltd., 1948-1950.; 18 items. (Box 106, Folder 22)
      Checks, invoices, and letters
    - Falcon Press., 1947-1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 23)
      Check and invoices
    - Four Seasons Book Shop., 1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 24)
      Checks and letter
    - Freedom Press., 1947-1948.; 10 items. (Box 106, Folder 25)
      Book lists, invoices, and letter
    - Freer Gallery of Art., 1948.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Gotham Book Mart, Inc., 1949 April 2.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Gramercy Book Shop., 1948.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Green Book Shop., 1948-1950.; 7 items. (Box 106, Folder 29)
    - Greenwood Press., 1948-1949.; 2 items. (Box 106, Folder 30)
      Check and invoice
    - Grey Walls Press Limited., 1949 January 6.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 31)
    - Hutchinson & Co., 1950.; 4 items. (Box 106, Folder 32)
    - Ivor Nicholson & Watson, Ltd., 1947-1948.; 2 items. (Box 106, Folder 33)
    - James Thin., 1950.; 4 items. (Box 106, Folder 34)
    - John Smith & Son, Ltd., 1950.; 5 items. (Box 106, Folder 35)
    - Jonathan Cape Ltd., 1950 April 19.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 36)
    - Joseph Vrin., 1950.; 10 items. (Box 106, Folder 37)
      Checks and invoices
    - Kaplanski, Boris., 1950.; 2 items. (Box 106, Folder 38)
      Letter and book list
    - Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co., 1949-1950.; 6 items. (Box 106, Folder 39)
      Invoices and letter
    - Librairie d'Amerique et d'Orient., 1950 February 28.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 40)
    - Librairie Lipton, Inc., 1950 June 9.; 2 items. (Box 106, Folder 41)
      Invoice and letter
    - Lion Book Shop., no date.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 42)
      Business card
    - Loliee, Marc., 1950 February 9.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 43)
    - Louis Tschann., 1940-1950.; 4 items. (Box 106, Folder 44)
      Check, invoices, and letter from D. Jonathan Grossman
    - Low's Bookstalls., 1950 May 1.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 45)
    - Luzac and Company Ltd., 1948-1949.; 5 items. (Box 106, Folder 46)
    - Metropolitan Book Store., 1948-1949.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 47)
      Business card and checks
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art., 1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 48)
      Checks
    - Miscellaneous., 1948-1950.; ca. 25 items. (Box 106, Folder 49)
      Assorted business cards, checks, postcards, book dealers and "wanted lists"
    - Mitsukoshi Limited., 1948 August 25.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 50)
    - Nedwick's Book Store., 1948-1949.; 6 items. (Box 106, Folder 51)
      Checks, invoices, and letter
    - New Directions., 1948-1950.; 7 items. (Box 106, Folder 52)
    - New Essays., 1948 March 1.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 53)
    - New York Graphic Society., 1948 September 21.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 54)
    - Orientalia, INC., 1948.; 7 items. (Box 106, Folder 55)
    - P.D. and Ione Perkins., 1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 56)
      Check, invoice and letter
    - Paul Elder and Company., 1948.; 7 items. (Box 106, Folder 57)
    - Paragon Book Gallery., 1948 September 8.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 58)
    - Presses Universitaires de France., 1950 June 21.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 59)
    - Pyetell's Book Shop., 1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 60)
      Check, invoice, and letter
    - Routledge and Kegan Paul Ltd., 1948-1950.; ca. 20 items. (Box 106, Folder 61)
    - Samuel J. Hume, INC., 1948.; 4 items. (Box 106, Folder 62)
    - Schulte's Book Store, INC., 1948-1950.; 7 items. (Box 106, Folder 63)
    - Socino Press Ltd., 1948 September 29.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 64)
    - T. & T. Clark, Publishers., 1948.; 5 items. (Box 106, Folder 65)
    - Tate Gallery., 1948 June 29.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 66)
    - Theodore Fillipi., 1948.; 3 items. (Box 106, Folder 67)
    - University of Chicago Oriental Institute., 1948 August 7.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 68)
    - University of New Mexico Press., 1948 August 5.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 69)
    - University of Notre Dame., 1948 August 6.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 70)
    - W. & G. Foyle Ltd., 1949-1950.; 8 items. (Box 106, Folder 71)
    - W. Heffer and Sons Ltd., 1950-1951.; 2 items. (Box 106, Folder 72)
      Letter and invoice
    - Yale University Press., 1948 August 9.; 1 item. (Box 106, Folder 73)
  - Subseries 5E: Photographs, 1925-1958; 1 folder.
    Assorted black and white photographs of Kenneth Rexroth, his family, and members of his circle (such as Henry Miller), mostly unlabeled.
    - Photographs., 1925-1958.; ca. 50 items. (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 5F: Travel,., 1948-1974; 3.5 boxes.
    Correspondence, ephemera and maps from Rexroth's travels. The Japan folders include correspondence related to the Japanese P.E.N. Society, international conferences, and fellowship and living arrangements.
    - Airline and ticket ephemera., 1957-1960.; ca. 25 items. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Afghanistan., no date.; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Amsterdam., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Australia., 1967.; 10 items. (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Belgium., 1966-1967.; 1 item. (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - China., 1967-1975.; 10 items. (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - England., 1949-1967.; 5 items. (Box 107, Folder 8)
      Includes a list of European contacts.
    - Finland., 1967-1969.; 10 items. (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - France., ca. 1967.; 3 items. (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Germany (folder 1 of 2)., 1966-1967.; 10 items. (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Germany (folder 2 of 2)., 1966-1967.; 19 items. (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Greece., ca. 1961. (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - India., 1967.; 5 items. (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Iran., ca. 1967.; 10 items. (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Italy., 1966-1969.; 16 items. (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Japan., ca. 1967-1974.; ca. 10 items. (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Japan., ca. 1967-1974.; ca. 45 items. (Box 109, Folder 1-5)
      Includes poems from a joint reading by Kenneth Rexroth and Shuntaro Tanikawa.
    - Spain., 1967-1969.; 5 items. (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Sweden., 1966.; 6 items. (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Tasmania., ca. 1967.; 2 items. (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Thailand., 1967.; 3 items. (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Turkey., 1966.; 6 items. (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - United States., 1948-1970.; 6 items. (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Series 6: Printed materials, 1936-1976; 36 boxes (18 linear ft.).
  A. Articles and essays, 1946-1975 (3.5 boxes).
  B. Clippings and reviews, 1936-1975 (3 boxes).
  C. Ephemera, 1940-1974 (10 boxes).
  D. Little magazines, 1936-1976 (8 boxes).
  E. Newspapers, 1938-1975 (5 boxes).
  F. Periodicals and newsletters, 1944-1975 (6.5 boxes).
  - Subseries 6A: Articles and essays,., 1946-1975; 3.5 boxes.
    Copies and reprints of published articles and essays by Rexroth and others. Arranged alphabetically by the surname of the author. Rexroth's articles, consisting largely of clippings from published newspaper columns, are further arranged into alphabetical files by the title of the piece. For a scrapbook of clippings of Rexroth's "Classics Revisited" column, see box 157.
    - Axelrod, Joseph., 1967.; 2 items. (Box 110, Folder 7)
      "An experimental college model"; NDEA foreign language institute programs
    - Barron, Frank., 1953.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 8)
      "Some personality correlates of independence of judgment"
    - Burnshaw, Stanley., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 9)
      "The body makes the minde"
    - Carruth, Hayden., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 10)
      "Making it new"
    - Cornell, Julian., 1953.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 11)
      "What you should know about avalanches"
    - Cottam, Clarence., 1963. (Box 110, Folder 12)
      "Commentary on Silent Spring"
    - Dennes, William., 1946.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 13)
      "Conflict"
    - Design Consultants Engineering Corp., 1966 February.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 14)
      Report: "Supplement to the San Francisco city-state joint freeway study on the Panhandle and Golden Gate freeways "
    - Dolwig, Richard J., 1965 February.; 2 items. (Box 110, Folder 15)
      "Reapportionment of the state legislature"; and "Division of California" by Robert N Bulla (1907)
    - Droz, Clement., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 16)
      "Posterity is just around the corner--or is it?"
    - Dunning, Stephen., 1966.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 17)
      "The economic situation of the poet: a professional problem?"
    - Farber, Leslie H., 1956.; 1 item. (Box 110, Folder 18)
      "Martin Buber and psychiatry"
    - Flint, F. Cudworth., no date.; 2 items. (Box 112, Folder 2)
      "Comments on recent poetry"
    - Fry, William., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 3)
      "Down the up market"
    - Goncalves, Ricardo M., 1968.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 4)
      "O Budismo tantrico no Japao"
    - Grigsby, Gordon K., 1971.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 5)
      "The presence of reality: the poetry of Kenneth Rexroth"
    - Hagen, Carlos., 1967 April.; 2 items. (Box 112, Folder 6)
      Proposals presented to the 1966 meeting of the Association for Recorded Sound Collections held at Washington, D.C., USA
    - Holmes, John., 1957.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 7)
      "John Ciardi"
    - Hoover, Glenn E., no date.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 8)
      "Evolutionary socialism, syndicalism, guild socialism and anarchism"
    - Junkins, Donald., 1967.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 9)
      "Creeley and Rexroth: no simple poets"
    - Kadushin, Charles., 1972.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 10)
      "Who are the elite intellectuals?"
    - Laitinen, Kai., 1962.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 11)
      "Vaino Linna and Veijo Meri, two aspects of war"
    - Loran, M.R., 1963.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 12)
      "Population dynamics of intestinal epithelia in the rat two months after partial resection of the ileum"
    - Malkoff, Karl., 1970.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 13)
      "Poetry of vision, poetry of action"
    - Marhenke, Paul., no date.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 14)
      "McTaggart's analysis of time"
    - McKenna, J. Fenton., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 15)
      "The care and feeding of the arts"
    - M.H. De Young Memorial Museum., 1966 March 1.; 2 items. (Box 112, Folder 16)
      Resignation statement by Miriam and Charles Lindstrom.
    - Miner, Earl Roy., no date.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 17)
      "The technique of Japanese poetry"
    - Nesbit, Louis., 1950.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 18)
      "The Jewish contribution to Argentine literature"
    - Nieto, Eva Margarita., no date.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 19)
      "The emergence of the persona in the poetry of Neruda"
    - Oden, G.C., 1965 June 16.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 20)
      "Relatively yours" (essay in response to Rexroth's comments on black vs white)
    - Oelschlager, Victor R.B., 1965.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 21)
      "Quixotessence"
    - Ong, Walter J., 1969.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 22)
      "Crisis and understanding in the humanities"
    - Parr, Albert., 1972-1973.; 3 items. (Box 112, Folder 23)
      Assorted reprints and articles.
    - Powell, Lawrence Clark., 1952-1954.; 2 items. (Box 112, Folder 24)
      "Transcontinental"; "The excitement of administration"
    - Proby, J.C.P., no date.; 1 item. (Box 112, Folder 25)